# YUSUF CEYLAN

## STUDENT 3D AND VFX ARTIST

#### CONTACT

\_\_ d

roma.

josefceylan2001@gmail.com



thebytwa.github.io



http://www.linkedin.com/in/y usuftceylan/

#### SKILLS

3d, 2D Design

3d, 2D Animation

Shaders and Texturing

Blender,

FL Studio, Bandlab

Unity, Unreal Engine

Html, Css, JavaScript

C#,

011,

September 2021 - present UNIVERSITY OF GREENWICH BSc Games Design and Development

#### LANGUAGES

English





#### PROFILE

I am currently a Games development student at the University of Greenwich, specializing in VFX, 3D-2D modeling, and animation. I am passionate about developing video games, specifically when it comes to making artwork in games. I have experienced challenges that come with a team and developed myself by attending group projects and game jams at the university. However, I have specifically experienced teamwork under stress with limited time in the places I have worked. I am currently working as a part-time worker.

### EXPERIENCE

### 3D and Logo Designer

Нуре

2024 - present

- I made 3D models and animations for a small amount of people in a team called hype.
- It is a small newly formed group that arranges parties mostly for university students in Turkey
- It was a project that required me to model a 3D model of their name and animate to be used to advertise the team.
- I was also asked to design their logo for social media accounst, which is where they connect with people.
- The 3D scenes and the logo are being used on the social media account.
- The group is formed by young university students who are specialised on different areas such as music, social media, environment design, and 3D and 2D designs

# 3D, Game and Level Designer, Programmer, Visual And Sound Artist

Phaze

2022 - 2023

- For this project, I intended to make a simple 3D platformer puzzle game in a team of 3 people.
- My job was to combine some of mine and other 3rd party assets for the level design.
- The other 2 members of the team had left the project after a short while so I had to finish the game alone.
- I have programmed most of the mechanics and designed the levels as well as the environment of them.
- Made a music fot he game and added simple sounds.



# YUSUF CEYLAN

## STUDENT 3D AND VFX ARTIST

### WORK EXPERIENCE

## Chef, Manager

Zuzu Bistro Bar

2021-2023

- I worked in a small kitchen for approximately 2 years where I learned new skills at the first and started managing the place it after a while.
- Worked under pressure with limited time.
- One of my jobs was to teach the new employers how everything worked and help them gain the skills required to work efficiently.
- Since it was a small place, I learned how to get a work done by myself and solve problems without having anyone to get help from.

#### HOBBIES

- Playing games
- Producing sounds and musics for games
- Producing music for cinematics
- Reading
- Training
- · Watching videos about science
- Drawing
- Watching Movies